+91 -8287813376

nishanttomar48@gmail.com

Nishant Portfolio

Nishant Tomar

Product Design Intern

My focus is always to hit the right spot between user and data to provide the right solution to the right problem. My specialization lies in designing mobile and website user interfaces professionally along with that I also have some knowledge of the code.

EXPERIENCE

Retrac

Sept, 2021 - Feb, 2022

UI/UX Design Intern

- Worked closely with engineering, developer teams and stakeholders to improve the overall user experience of Version 2 and made some iteration in version 1 which resulted in getting their first customer onboarded.

Pankh - wings that connect

Sept, 2021 - Nov, 2021

User Experience Designer

- Conducted User Survey, designed wireframes, Mockups, developed fully functional Prototypes and tested user interface and user flow to ensure quality

Dark Code

July, 2021 - Sept, 2022

Visual Designer

- Responsible for designing user interface mockups based on UX requirements
- Worked on multiple design iteration to ensure the client was satisfied with results

Docplus

Jan, 2021 - Apr, 2021

Visual Designer

- College Startup associated with BITS Goa
- Designed the first Iteration for it's web version

FRUITABLEZ

August, 2021

Visual Designer (Freelance)

- Researched for the user's need to make User Experience Better
- Designed user interface mockups visuals for application

Caravan Electrical Solutions

May, 2021 - Jul, 2021

UI Designer (Freelance)

- Created UX specifications, personas, scenarios, flowcharts, and prototype
- Designed wireframes, mockups and developed the website

EDUCATION

CLUSTER INNOVATION CENTER, UNIVERSITY OF DELHI

S.P.G.A - 9.3 (till Sem - 3)

B.Tech in Information Technology and Mathematical Innovation

Major: IT & Mathematics, Minor: Management

Salwan Public School

___ 2008-2019

High School(C.B.S.E.) - 96 %

Senior Secondary School(C.B.S.E.) - 92.3 %

SKILLS

HTML, CSS

FIND ME ON

Figma

User Research

Visual Design

Prototyping

Behance: https://www.behance.net/nishanttomar1

Github: https://github.com/nishanttomar48

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nishant-tomar-du/